{
  "Name": "Katakana",
  "Description": "A set for learning the Japanese syllabary - Katakana. On one side is a syllabe in the Katakana, and on the other is its Romaji transcription. Source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Katakana",
  "Cards": [
    {
      "Question": "ア",
      "Answer": "a"
    },
	{
      "Question": "イ",
      "Answer": "i"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ウ",
      "Answer": "u"
    },
	{
      "Question": "エ",
      "Answer": "e"
    },
	{
      "Question": "オ",
      "Answer": "o"
    },
	{
      "Question": "カ",
      "Answer": "ka"
    },
	{
      "Question": "キ",
      "Answer": "ki"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ク",
      "Answer": "ku"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ケ",
      "Answer": "ke"
    },
	{
      "Question": "コ",
      "Answer": "ko"
    },
	{
      "Question": "サ",
      "Answer": "sa"
    },
	{
      "Question": "シ",
      "Answer": "shi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ス",
      "Answer": "su"
    },
	{
      "Question": "セ",
      "Answer": "se"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ソ",
      "Answer": "so"
    },
	{
      "Question": "タ",
      "Answer": "ta"
    },
	{
      "Question": "チ",
      "Answer": "chi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ツ",
      "Answer": "tsu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "テ",
      "Answer": "te"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ト",
      "Answer": "to"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ナ",
      "Answer": "na"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ニ",
      "Answer": "ni"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヌ",
      "Answer": "nu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ネ",
      "Answer": "ne"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ノ",
      "Answer": "no"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ハ",
      "Answer": "ha"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヒ",
      "Answer": "hi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "フ",
      "Answer": "fu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヘ",
      "Answer": "he"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ホ",
      "Answer": "ho"
    },
	{
      "Question": "マ",
      "Answer": "ma"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ミ",
      "Answer": "mi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ム",
      "Answer": "mu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "メ",
      "Answer": "me"
    },
	{
      "Question": "モ",
      "Answer": "mo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヤ",
      "Answer": "ya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ユ",
      "Answer": "yu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "エ",
      "Answer": "ye"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヨ",
      "Answer": "yo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ラ",
      "Answer": "ra"
    },
	{
      "Question": "リ",
      "Answer": "ri"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ル",
      "Answer": "ru"
    },
	{
      "Question": "レ",
      "Answer": "re"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ロ",
      "Answer": "ro"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ワ",
      "Answer": "wa"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヰ",
      "Answer": "wi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヱ",
      "Answer": "we"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヲ",
      "Answer": "wo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "キャ",
      "Answer": "kya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "キュ",
      "Answer": "kyu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "キョ",
      "Answer": "kyo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "シャ",
      "Answer": "sha"
    },
	{
      "Question": "シュ",
      "Answer": "shu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ショ",
      "Answer": "sho"
    },
	{
      "Question": "チャ",
      "Answer": "cha"
    },
	{
      "Question": "チュ",
      "Answer": "chu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "チョ",
      "Answer": "cho"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ニャ",
      "Answer": "nya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ニュ",
      "Answer": "nyu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ニョ",
      "Answer": "nyo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヒャ",
      "Answer": "hya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヒュ",
      "Answer": "hyu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヒョ",
      "Answer": "hyo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ミャ",
      "Answer": "mya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ミュ",
      "Answer": "myu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ミョ",
      "Answer": "myo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "リャ",
      "Answer": "rya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "リュ",
      "Answer": "ryu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "リョ",
      "Answer": "ryo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ガ",
      "Answer": "ga"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ギ",
      "Answer": "gi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "グ",
      "Answer": "gu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ゲ",
      "Answer": "ge"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ゴ",
      "Answer": "go"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ザ",
      "Answer": "za"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ジ",
      "Answer": "ji"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ズ",
      "Answer": "zu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ゼ",
      "Answer": "ze"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ゾ",
      "Answer": "zo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ダ",
      "Answer": "da"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヂ",
      "Answer": "ji"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヅ",
      "Answer": "zu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "デ",
      "Answer": "de"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ド",
      "Answer": "do"
    },
	{
      "Question": "バ",
      "Answer": "ba"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ビ",
      "Answer": "bi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ブ",
      "Answer": "bu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ベ",
      "Answer": "be"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ボ",
      "Answer": "bo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "パ",
      "Answer": "pa"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ピ",
      "Answer": "pi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "プ",
      "Answer": "pu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ペ",
      "Answer": "pe"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ポ",
      "Answer": "po"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ギャ",
      "Answer": "gya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ギュ",
      "Answer": "gyu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ギョ",
      "Answer": "gyo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ジャ",
      "Answer": "ja"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ジュ",
      "Answer": "ju"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ジョ",
      "Answer": "jo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヂャ",
      "Answer": "ja"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヂュ",
      "Answer": "ju"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ヂョ",
      "Answer": "jo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ビャ",
      "Answer": "bya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ビュ",
      "Answer": "byu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ビョ",
      "Answer": "byo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ピャ",
      "Answer": "pya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ピュ",
      "Answer": "pyu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ピョ",
      "Answer": "pyo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ン",
      "Answer": "n"
    }
  ]
}